Is anyone else here getting nervous?
Try to stay calm.
Times like these require us to keep
our heads on straight and be prepared.
Putting this stuff on with only one hand
is a lot harder than I thought it'd be.
Alright, before we leave, has
anyone here ever scuba-dyed before?
Not me. No.
No, I haven't.
You have to teach us how to
use this equipment right now.
That thing is going to
attack us any second!
Try and calm yourself, Avdol.
You must never panic, no matter what.
That is the most important
rule when scuba diving.
When you're traveling underwater, for
every 10 meters you go below the surface,
the corresponding pressure
increases along with you.
The surface pressure
starts at 1 atmosphere,
and since we're 40
meters below the surface,
we'll endure 5 atmospheres of pressure.
If we surface too quickly,
the pressure will cause our
lungs and blood vessels to burst.
We have to rise slowly
so our bodies can adjust.
Since we're nearing the Egyptian coast,
it's best to ascend along the sea floor.
Okay, I'm letting the water in.
Now pay very close attention.
What you're looking at is a regulator.
The valve inside only allows air
in from the tank when you inhale.
The air you breathe out exits
through the piece on the left.
Wait a second, what about spit?
What happens if I need to drool or
have to huck a loogie or something?
Stuff like that just comes
out of the opening here.
By the way, this should go without
saying, but we can't talk underwater.
Instead, we'll use hand signals.
Let's keep things simple and only use two.
When things are going smoothly,
we'll use this to say okay.
But when they aren't, use this.
Mr.
Joestar, couldn't we just use our
stands to communicate underwater?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
I didn't think about that.
Oh, man!
And I was just about to say that
I Know a really good hand signal.
He says, "Your underwear
is showing." Yeah,
we could Be attacked
and killed at any time.
Stop fooling around and let's go.
This room is is about to be
filled to the brim with water.
Put on your masks and regulators
while you still have time.
Polnareff!
ng ng ng and
the
next one,
the star dance?
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
We'll
be
right back.
But, when did it?
That's it.
The stand had already
integrated with the regulator.
That bastard.
It's gonna rip him apart from the inside.
We've gotta drain the
room while we still can.
It's too late.
It must have been lying in
wait for just this moment.
Damn it.
It's already burrowing down his throat.
We can't just stand here
watching him like this.
What should we do?
Pyrofad Green!
Urban Purple!
What are you doing?
I was able to grab it before
it could damage his organs.
Me too.
Let's pull it out before it transforms.
Success!
All right.
Keep it just like that.
Look!
It's transforming into something else!
You've got to be kidding me!
It turned into a spear gun?
Emerald Splash!
Silver Tyrion!
Let's get movie it's already
reloading it doesn't quit.
Hurry.
Move it old man yeah i'm coming.
That was too close for comfort.
It's too soon for us to relax.
Especially since that bastard knows
exactly how to hit us where it hurts most.
Polnareff, are you alright?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
You guys saved my life back there.
Merci beaucoup.
Wow, just look at how
beautiful it is down here.
This would have been a spectacular
place to visit on vacation.
This isn't time to plan your next getaway.
We have to surface before
we run out of oxygen.
Think we're safe?
I believe so.
The high priestess can
transform into metals and glass,
but it can't take the
form of bubbles or fish?
so I doubt it'll come after us.
Just keep your eyes peeled.
If it pursues us, it'll probably transform
into a screw on our gear to do it.
Be careful of moving
pebbles and stones, too.
Look up there!
I think it's a sea tunnel.
We're at seven meters.
We've finally reached the Egyptian shore.
We can swim along these
rocks to get to the surface.
What is that?
Yes, it's definitely the stand.
It merged with the sea
floor, and it's Norgantuan.
Damn, there's no way
we can fight this pool.
This is impossible!
How is it so gigantic?
What the hell?
It was so small earlier!
What's this dance power?
Man, I'm too confused!
You boys are so slow on the uptake!
Didn't it ever cross your mind
that if the rocks are mineral,
it would mean the seabed
is mostly mineral as well?
Yes, of course.
That's why the stand has
suddenly gotten stronger.
Its user must be nearby, and I'd
wager she's closer than we think.
You guessed it, and to be more precise,
I'm seven meters above you on the shore.
But since you're about to be ground
to bits by my high priestess,
you'll never have the
chance to see my face.
So long!
It's so dark in here.
I can't tell what part
of the stand we're in.
Seems like we're still inside its mouth.
But luckily, we weren't
sucked down its gullet.
Yoo-hoo! Jotaro!
Believe it or not,
you're actually my type.
So this is going to be as painful for
me as for you, but despite my feelings!
I still have to make the
high priestess digest you.
How sad if only our encounter
had been under different?
Circumstances, but if I kill you lord
deal will no doubt shower me with praise.
So don't hate me
Good grief do I have to
would you just say it
come on hurry up and
get on with it say what?
Ah, I see.
It's a shame things turned out this way.
I would have liked to have seen
your face, if only this once.
You might have been my type, too.
And if you were, well, I just
might have fallen for you.
Oh, hey!
You know what, guys?
I bet she's a beauty.
I can tell from that
gorgeous voice of hers.
She comes across as an elegant woman.
My fortune teller's instinct senses it.
Well, if you ask me, she sounds
just like Audrey Hepburn.
Man, if I were only 30 years younger.
You bastards didn't mean
a single word of that!
I'll kill you all!
Holy shit!
Everyone, look!
What is that?
It looks like a tongue.
The Stan's tongue, to be exact.
Here it comes! Jotaro!
Jotaro!
Clove!
No, Jotaro's going to land in...
He...
He landed right on the bowlers!
Jotaro, get out of there now!
You're about to be crushed!
You want to pick your
strength against mine, do you?
Damn, what ridiculous power!
Oh, give up, Jotaro!
Those teeth are as hard as diamonds!
You'll never be able to break them!
It's time for you to meet your end!
We have to save Jokoro!
Stay out of my way!
That damn tongue again!
Magicians, run!
We're out of time!
We have to free him!
Jotaro!
No!
Those giant teeth pulverized him!
Jo... Jotaro...
We didn't make it in time.
Hold on a sec.
I think I can hear something.
It's definitely coming from
far away. Listen again.
I think it's getting closer.
Wait, that voice belongs to...
The teeth!
It's coming from inside the teeth!
Huh?
Everyone, get down and
brace yourselves! Huh?
Those teeth were hot as diamonds,
but he managed to punch his way out!
Oh, my God!
And would you look at that?
He's breaking the other
teeth while he's at it!
That show-off.
His stance amidst power
never ceases to amaze me.
Come on.
I'm getting us out of this hellhole.
Ah, good grief.
Well, you were right about those teeth being
sturdy, but they weren't sturdy enough.
Too bad.
I guess your so-called diamonds
were a little low on calcium.
You couldn't pay me to do that again, hmm?
Hey, there's a woman
passed out over there.
I assume it's Rose, the
user of the High Priestess.
She doesn't seem dangerous.
Should we just leave her?
I think I'll go see if she's hot or not.
From the looks of it, she's
got a pretty nice body.
Let's see.
How's it going over there, Polnareff?
Nothing to see here, folks!
No comment whatsoever!
Trust me, you don't want to see her.
Pratival, there's no
point in looking. I see.
It hasn't been easy, but we
finally made it to Egypt.
Indeed.
A trip that would have
taken a mere 20 hours
by plane ended up taking
a whopping 30 days.
It's been quite the adventure.
We've gone inside a brain and even
inside our dreams. Our dreams?
What do you mean, Kakyoin?
Why are you talking about dreams?
It's morning.
Wake up already. Oh, right.
You guys don't remember that.
Huh?
Whatever. Let's go.
Five mysterious and otherworldly stands.
Powered by the mystical and
symbolized by the tarot.
Joseph Joestar once described their
journey as around the world in 80 days.
From Tokyo to Hong Kong,
they faced Tower of Grey.
In Southeast Asia, they tackled
dark blue moon and strength.
In Singapore, they encountered
ebony devil and yellow temperance.
In Calcutta, India, it was
hanged man and emperor.
In Varanasi, India, the Empress.
And near the Pakistani border,
they fought Wheel of Fortune.
In the mountains of Pakistan,
they battled justice.
In Karachi, Pakistan, the Lovers.
In the desert of the United
Arab Emirates, the Sun.
And in Saudi Arabia, Death 13.
On a small island in
the Red Sea, Judgment.
And now on the Red Sea floor,
they've just defeated High Priestess.
With several of Dio's
assassins vanquished.
They have finally arrived in Egypt!
Only a few of the tarot
cards still remain.
But little do Jojo and company know?
New threats lie ahead in Egypt!
Ready to take our heroes on!
That's one!
Two!
Three!
Nine!
There are nine in all, both genders.
What the…
what the hell was that?
Have the meddlesome flies
swarming around been swatted?
That speed wagon foundation.
For pity's sake, I can't let
my guard down for a minute.
I must say, I've gotten
quite used to this body.
Tell me, Jonathan, can you feel it?
Your descendants are inching ever closer.
It can be so cruel and unforgiving,
this wretched little world of ours.
So that's what's been going on!
Why didn't you just tell me Jotaro
was helping you with your work?
That's fantastic!
The boy still has a long
way to go compared to me so
this work is important enough
for you to ask for help.
That's right.
It's my most important mission yet, and
it's imperative that we don't mess up.
But as long as we work together, we should
get it done without too much trouble.
Say Joseph could I speak to Jotaro?
Yeah, sure, but what do you want to talk
to him about nothing much is it wrong?
That I want to hear my darling
grandson's voice well no Jotaro it's for
you hey it's me grandpa Told me
everything Jotaro work hard and take care
of your grandfather for me will do I
know in my Heart if you work together
you Joestar men can overcome just
about any hardship that comes your
No way.
I truly believe that.
Grandma Susie, you...
What's the matter?
You sound so serious all of a sudden.
It's nothing.
All right, I'm hanging up.
I look forward to good news. Ciao!
Madam. Hmm?
It's hard for me to believe it,
but at this point it's
already been 30 years
that I've worked for the Joestar family.
But I can honestly say that we've never
faced something of this magnitude.
Oh, come now.
You're overreacting.
Didn't he say it was just
a little business trip?
Well, I suppose so.
It's so troublesome when men act
selfish and refuse to tell us anything.
But I've grown accustomed to it.
The Joestar family has been
like this for an entire century.
I'm sure if she were here, she'd say
the same thing and laugh it all off.
Hmm?
What's the matter, Jotaro?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
All right, it's time to head out.
After a century,
it's time for us Joestars to bring
an end to Dio's grip on our family.
But we don't have to do it alone.
Hey, Mr. Joestar!
We got the car that you asked us to buy.
Let's hurry and hit the road.
We should probably get to where
we're going before it gets too dark.
Well, old man, okay, you're right.
Guess we're pretty lucky, huh?
Yeah, yeah, hold your horses.
We're coming.
This is the land of Egypt,
a nation that's 97 % desert.
However,
thanks to the blessings of the Nile,
beautiful fertile green spreads
across the entirety of its riverbanks.
In addition to the culture
of the ancient Egyptians,
Egypt is also home to Persian, Greek,
Roman, Muslim, and Arabian cultures?
and all have left their indelible marks.
What bizarre adventures and
challenges await Jotaro and the others
in this eternal land as they
continue their perilous journey.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If you move too quick.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got their money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling types with a hookah. I say.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink.
Then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say. Walk
like
an Egyptian.